

Febby Nurfitriyani

Web Developer / Designer

⊗ CONTACTS

ADDRESS

Bandung, Indonesia

PHONE 0895375066317

EMAIL febbynurfitriyani1208@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Politeknik Pos Indonesia (2014-2018) Bachelor Degree, IT GPA: 3.72 (Scale 4,00)

SKILL

Frontend Developer:
CSS, Bootstrap, ReactJS, Javascript
Backend Developer:

PHP, Laravel Database :

MySQL, Firebase, Firebird

SOCIAL MEDIA

Website

https://febbynurfitriyani.com/

Blog

https://ranialmonk.blogspot.com/

Linkedin

Linkedin.com/febby-nurfitriyani-4a2709118/

Instagram

instagram.com/fbbynftryn

PROFILE

Hello! My name is Febby Nurfitriyani. I'm Web developer with 3 Years Experience. Very interested in design and web-based application development or desktops. I am hardworking and active organize. This is to state that above information is true and provided here by me, all in good faith.

EXPERIENCE

2016 O Volunteer PON Jabar

as a contingent volunteer

2017 O PT Zamrud Khatulistiwa Technology

I am part of a team working on designing a svara (backend) application. The svara application is a radio application and is owned by a startup native to Indonesia. This app is built with React S and MongoDB

2018 O Politeknik Pos Indonesia

I am part of a team working on designing a svara (backend) application. The svara application is a radio application and is owned by a startup native to Indonesia. This app is built with ReactJS and MongoDB

2018 - Now O PT Mewah Niagajaya

Build the PT Mewah Niagajaya intranet application using Laravel and Firebird. This application is an information system in managing and processing data according to company needs. Technologies used: Framework Laravel 5.1, Docker, Vagrant, Flamerobin(Firebird)

PORTOFOLIO

2018 - Now O ERP Intranet

Application that manages the entire production process of the company. Built using Laravel and Firebird.

2018 - Now O Dyeing Schedule

Monitoring application in real time. Built using Javascript and Firebird.

2018 O Call Poseidon

Call Poseidon is an IoT-based smart tool. Built with Arduino, Firebase, Laravel 5.6 and Android.

2017 O Svara

Backend of PT Zamrud's svara radio application. Built with the ReactJS and MongoDB frameworks.